<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>NASA Image of the Day</title>
	<description>The latest NASA "Image of the Day" image.</description>
	<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-of-the-day/</link>
	<ns0:link href="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<language>en-us</language>
	<managingEditor>brian.dunbar@nasa.gov (Brian Dunbar)</managingEditor>
	<webMaster>brian.dunbar@nasa.gov (Brian Dunbar)</webMaster>
	<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<item>
			<title>Intuitive Machines-2 Lifts Off</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-988/</link>
			<description>Creating a golden streak in the night sky, a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket carrying Intuitive Machines’ Nova-C lunar lander (IM-2) soars upward after liftoff from Launch Complex 39A at NASA’s Kennedy Space Center in Florida at 7:16 p.m. EST Wednesday, Feb. 26 as part of NASA’s CLPS (Commercial Lunar Payload Services) initiative. The IM-2 launch is carrying NASA science, technology demonstrations, and other commercial payloads to Mons Mouton, a lunar plateau to advance our understanding of the Moon and planetary processes, while paving the way for future crewed missions.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_1.jpg" length="4479477" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-988/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:29 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Milky Way on the Horizon</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gmt029_06_47_don-pettit_ost-fwd-dragon-2/</link>
			<description>The Milky Way appears beyond Earth's horizon in this celestial photograph captured on Jan. 29, 2025, by NASA astronaut Don Pettit using a camera with low light and long duration settings pointed out a window on the SpaceX Dragon crew spacecraft. The International Space Station was orbiting 265 miles above the Pacific Ocean off the coast of Chile just before sunrise.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_2.jpg" length="18039909" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gmt029_06_47_don-pettit_ost-fwd-dragon-2/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:38 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Diamonds from NASA’s X-59</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/nasas-x-59-displays-mach-diamonds-at-maximum-afterburner/</link>
			<description>NASA’s X-59 lights up the night sky with its unique Mach diamonds, also known as shock diamonds, during maximum afterburner testing at Lockheed Martin Skunk Works in Palmdale, California. The test demonstrates the engine’s ability to generate the thrust required for supersonic flight, advancing NASA’s Quesst mission.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_3.jpg" length="10307344" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/nasas-x-59-displays-mach-diamonds-at-maximum-afterburner/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 17:23 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Venus Blows Off Some Steam</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/arc-1977-ac77-0475-7orig/</link>
			<description>Tall plumes of white vapor rise from the rocky Venusian surface in this April 19, 1977, artist’s concept.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_4.jpg" length="6886815" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/arc-1977-ac77-0475-7orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:20 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hubble Captures a Cosmic Cloudscape</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/cosmic-cloudscape/</link>
			<description>This NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope reveals clouds of gas and dust near the Tarantula Nebula, located in the Large Magellanic Cloud about 160,000 light-years away.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_5.jpg" length="3618340" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/cosmic-cloudscape/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 20:37 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Artemis II Rocket Booster Stacking Complete</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-981/</link>
			<description>Engineers with NASA’s Exploration Ground Systems complete stacking operations on the twin SLS (Space Launch System) solid rocket boosters for Artemis II by integrating the nose cones atop the forward assemblies inside the Vehicle Assembly Building’s High Bay 3 at NASA’s Kennedy Space Center in Florida on Wednesday, Feb. 19, 2025. The twin solid boosters will help support the remaining rocket components and the Orion spacecraft during final assembly of the Artemis II Moon rocket and provide more than 75 percent of the total SLS thrust during liftoff from NASA Kennedy’s Launch Pad 39B.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_6.jpg" length="19677123" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-981/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:03 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Our Pale Blue Dot</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/49533887268-9d045c7081-o/</link>
			<description>This updated version of "the Pale Blue Dot," made for the photo's 30th anniversary in 2020, uses modern image-processing software and techniques to revisit the well-known Voyager view while attempting to respect the original data and intent of those who planned the images.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_7.jpg" length="632741" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/49533887268-9d045c7081-o/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 19:05 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A Stellar Bouquet</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/30dorlarge/</link>
			<description>This composite image contains the deepest X-ray image ever made of the spectacular star forming region called 30 Doradus. By combining X-ray data from NASA’s Chandra X-ray Observatory (blue and green) with optical data from NASA’s Hubble Space Telescope (yellow) and radio data from the Atacama Large Millimeter/submillimeter Array (orange), this stellar arrangement comes alive.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_8.jpg" length="171974" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/30dorlarge/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 17:37 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Giving NASA's CADRE a Hand</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia26427orig/</link>
			<description>One of three small lunar rovers that are part of a NASA technology demonstration called CADRE (Cooperative Autonomous Distributed Robotic Exploration) is prepared for shipping in a clean room at the agency's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Southern California on Jan. 29, 2025.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_9.jpg" length="8701405" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia26427orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 18:38 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A Rainbow-colored “Feather” in the Martian Sky</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia25740orig/</link>
			<description>NASA's Curiosity Mars rover captured this feather-shaped iridescent cloud just after sunset on Jan. 27, 2023, the 3,724th Martian day, or sol, of the mission. Studying the colors in iridescent clouds tells scientists something about particle size within the clouds and how they grow over time. These clouds were captured as part of a follow-on imaging campaign to study noctilucent, or "night-shining" clouds, which started in 2021. This scene made up of 28 individual images captured by the rover's Mast Camera, or Mastcam.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_10.jpg" length="93376" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia25740orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 19:36 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Space Shuttle Endeavour Takes Flight</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ksc00pp0230orig/</link>
			<description>The brilliant exhaust from the solid rocket boosters (center) and blue mach diamonds from the main engine nozzles mark the launch of Space Shuttle Endeavour from Launch Pad 39A on Feb. 11, 2000.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_11.jpg" length="648832" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ksc00pp0230orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 22:21 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mount Everest from Space</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/sts080-733-001orig/</link>
			<description>This view from space shuttle Columbia shows Mount Everest, which reaches 29,028 feet in elevation (8,848 meters), along with many glaciers. Mount Everest is to the left of the V-shaped valley.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_12.jpg" length="4884575" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/sts080-733-001orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 22:11 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Golden Moon over the Superdome</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/wolf-moon-rises-over-the-superdome-in-new-orleans/</link>
			<description>The full moon rises over the Superdome and the city of New Orleans, Louisiana on Monday evening, January 13, 2025. The Wolf Moon, also known as the Ice or Cold Moon, was full at 5:27 p.m. EST. New Orleans is home to NASA’s Michoud Assembly Facility where several pieces of hardware for the SLS (Space Launch System) are being built.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_13.jpg" length="14155681" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/wolf-moon-rises-over-the-superdome-in-new-orleans/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:37 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Robot Gets a Grip</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gmt035_18_44_for-poic_suni-williams_astrobee/</link>
			<description>The blue tentacle-like arms containing gecko-like adhesive pads, attached to an Astrobee robotic free-flyer, reach out and grapple a "capture cube" inside the International Space Station's Kibo laboratory module. The experimental grippers, outfitted on the toaster-sized Astrobee, demonstrated autonomous detection and capture techniques that may be used to remove space debris and service satellites in low Earth orbit.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_14.jpg" length="8856724" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gmt035_18_44_for-poic_suni-williams_astrobee/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 20:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Apollo 14 Moon Landing</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/as14-66-09277orig/</link>
			<description>An excellent view of the Apollo 14 lunar module on the Moon, as photographed during the first Apollo 14 moonwalk on the lunar surface. The astronauts have already deployed the U.S. flag. While astronauts Alan B. Shepard Jr., commander, and Edgar D. Mitchell, lunar module pilot, descended in the lunar module to explore the Moon, astronaut Stuart A. Roosa, command module pilot, remained with the command and service modules in lunar orbit.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_15.jpg" length="3458211" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/as14-66-09277orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 20:05 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bullseye!</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/hubble-leda1313424-stsci-01jjadtmj80r1r4w6kk563rw2c/</link>
			<description>LEDA 1313424, aptly nicknamed the Bullseye, is two and a half times the size of our Milky Way and has nine rings — six more than any other known galaxy. High-resolution imagery from NASA’s Hubble Space Telescope confirmed eight rings, and data from the W. M. Keck Observatory in Hawaii confirmed a ninth. Hubble and Keck also confirmed which galaxy dove through the Bullseye, creating these rings: the blue dwarf galaxy that sits to its immediate center-left.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_16.jpg" length="5874504" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/hubble-leda1313424-stsci-01jjadtmj80r1r4w6kk563rw2c/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:03 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Stacking Artemis II</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-972/</link>
			<description>Engineers and technicians with NASA’s Exploration Ground Systems Program prepare to lift the left center center booster segment shown with the iconic NASA “worm” insignia for the agency’s SLS (Space Launch System) rocket to the Vehicle Assembly Building at NASA's Kennedy Space Center in Florida on Friday, Jan. 24, 2025.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_17.jpg" length="35192868" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-972/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:58 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Building an Antenna</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia26454orig/</link>
			<description>A crane lowers the 112-foot-wide (34-meter-wide) steel framework for the Deep Space Station 23 (DSS-23) reflector dish into position on Dec. 18, 2024, at the Deep Space Network's Goldstone Space Communications Complex near Barstow, California. A multi-frequency beam waveguide antenna, DSS-23 will boost the DSN's capacity and enhance NASA's deep space communications capabilities for decades to come.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_18.jpg" length="511788" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia26454orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 17:16 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>SPHEREx’s Concentric Cones</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia26542orig/</link>
			<description>NASA's SPHEREx observatory is oriented in a horizontal position, revealing all three layers of photon shields as well as the telescope. This photo was taken at BAE Systems in Boulder, Colorado, in April 2024.

Short for Spectro-Photometer for the History of the Universe, Epoch of Reionization and Ices Explorer, SPHEREx will create a map of the cosmos like no other. Using a technique called spectroscopy to image the entire sky in 102 wavelengths of infrared light, SPHEREx will gather information about the composition of and distance to millions of galaxies and stars. With this map, scientists will study what happened in the first fraction of a second after the big bang, how galaxies formed and evolved, and the origins of water in planetary systems in our galaxy.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_19.jpg" length="2015912" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia26542orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:37 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Geyser Season on Mars</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia22881orig/</link>
			<description>Springtime in the South Polar region of Mars is a season of exciting activity. The thick coating of carbon dioxide ice that accumulated over the winter begins to sublimate (turn to vapor) as the sun rises higher in the sky and warms the ice. Sunlight penetrates through the transparent ice, and is absorbed at the base of the ice layer. The gas that forms as a result of the warming escapes through weaknesses in the ice and erupts in the form of magnificent geysers of gas and dust.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_20.jpg" length="1204587" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia22881orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:15 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Wolf Moon in Washington</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/full-wolf-moon-rise/</link>
			<description>The full Moon, also known in January as the Wolf Moon, rises above the Lincoln Memorial and the Memorial Bridge, Monday, Jan. 13, 2025, as seen from Arlington, Virginia.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_21.jpg" length="11833905" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/full-wolf-moon-rise/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:53 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Get My Good Side</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-971/</link>
			<description>An inquisitive sandhill crane approaches the photographer near the Vehicle Assembly Building at NASA’s Kennedy Space Center in Florida on March 24, 2021. Kennedy shares space with the Merritt Island National Wildlife refuge, which is home to more than 1,000 species of plants, 117 species of fish, 68 amphibians and reptiles, 330 birds, and 31 different mammals. The refuge provides a favorable environment for sandhill cranes as it contains shallow freshwater habitats for nesting, along with a variety of vegetation and prey to feed on.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_22.jpg" length="24049231" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-971/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:34 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hubble Studies the Tarantula Nebula’s Outskirts</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/a-tarantulas-outskirts/</link>
			<description>This NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope image features a dusty yet sparkling scene from one of the Milky Way’s satellite galaxies, the Large Magellanic Cloud. The Large Magellanic Cloud is a dwarf galaxy situated about 160,000 light-years away in the constellations Dorado and Mensa.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_23.jpg" length="5087687" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/a-tarantulas-outskirts/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:10 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Artist’s Concept of Gemini Spacecraft</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/s65-14257orig/</link>
			<description>This is an artist's concept of a two-person Gemini spacecraft in flight, showing a cutaway view. The Gemini program was designed as a bridge between the Mercury and Apollo programs.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_24.jpg" length="1211771" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/s65-14257orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 22:20 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Suni Williams Conducts Spacewalk</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/iss072e487421/</link>
			<description>NASA astronaut and Expedition 72 commander Suni Williams is pictured during a spacewalk outside the International Space Station where she replaced a rate gyro assembly that helps maintain the orientation of the orbital outpost.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_25.jpg" length="2473872" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/iss072e487421/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/martin-luther-king-jr-memorial/</link>
			<description>The Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial is seen in the foreground with the Washington Monument in the background, Sunday, Jan. 5, 2025, in Washington. The memorial covers four acres and includes the Stone of Hope, a granite statue of civil rights movement leader Martin Luther King Jr. carved by sculptor Lei Yixin.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_26.jpg" length="12440156" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/martin-luther-king-jr-memorial/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:48 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hubble Reveals Jupiter in Ultraviolet Light</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/hubble-provides-unique-ultraviolet-view-of-jupiter-2/</link>
			<description>Released on Nov. 3, 2023, in honor of Jupiter reaching opposition, which occurs when the planet and the Sun are in opposite sides of the sky, this view of the gas giant planet includes the iconic, massive storm called the “Great Red Spot.”</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_27.jpg" length="482372" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/hubble-provides-unique-ultraviolet-view-of-jupiter-2/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Langley’s Propeller Research Tunnel</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/7605912294-f4e0b4eb2f-o/</link>
			<description>Chief of aerodynamics Elton W. Miller ponders the future of the Sperry M-1 Messenger, the first full-scale airplane tested in the Propeller Research Tunnel. Miller was one of the designers of the Propeller Research Tunnel.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_28.jpg" length="299604" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/7605912294-f4e0b4eb2f-o/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 19:35 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Best of 2024: Dinosaur Prepared to Safely Watch Solar Eclipse</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/nasa-at-the-childrens-museum-of-indianapolis/</link>
			<description>A visitor takes a picture of a sculpture of an adult Alamosaurus wearing solar glasses outside of The Children’s Museum of Indianapolis, Saturday, April 6, 2024, in Indianapolis, Ind. On Monday, April 8, 2024, a total solar eclipse swept across a narrow portion of the North American continent from Mexico’s Pacific coast to the Atlantic coast of Newfoundland, Canada.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_29.jpg" length="20843452" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/nasa-at-the-childrens-museum-of-indianapolis/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 18:43 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Earth in Far-Ultraviolet</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/s72-36972orig/</link>
			<description>A color enhancement of a far-ultraviolet photo of Earth taken by astronaut John W. Young, commander, with the ultraviolet camera on April 21, 1972. The original black-and-white photo was printed on Agfacontour film three times, each exposure recording only one light level. The three light levels were then colored blue (dimmest), green (next brightest), and red (brightest).</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_30.jpg" length="3366555" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/s72-36972orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 20:04 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Los Angeles Fires Seen from International Space Station</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gg6dnlmxqaaqfoe/</link>
			<description>On Jan. 10, 2025, NASA astronaut Don Pettit posted two images of the Los Angeles fires from the International Space Station.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_31.jpg" length="830506" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gg6dnlmxqaaqfoe/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 22:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Laboratory Director Tawnya Plummer Laughinghouse</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ceb-5997a/</link>
			<description>"As a young college student, it was the first time I ever faced [this situation], and it buckled me. It set me back until I realized that I could do it and that my worth wasn't based on what someone else thought of me or my abilities…If I had pulled myself out of that STEM major, I would never have been managing a technology demonstration program for NASA that launched ten technologies into space.” 
– Tawnya Plummer Laughinghouse, Director of the Materials and Processes Laboratory, Engineering Directorate, NASA’s Marshall Space Flight Center </description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_32.jpg" length="1188752" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ceb-5997a/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 19:07 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Best of 2024: Reestablished NASA Art Program Begins with Mural in New York City</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/nasa-reestablishes-historical-art-program-with-space-themed-mural-4/</link>
			<description>The New York-based artist team Geraluz, left, and WERC, right, and their son Amaru Alvarez, 5, pose for picture with the mural “To the Moon, and Back” by the artist team that was created as part of the reimagined NASA Art Program, Tuesday, September 24, 2024, at 350 Hudson Street in New York City. The murals use geometrical patterns to invite deeper reflection on the exploration, creativity, and connection with the cosmos.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_33.jpg" length="25342292" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/nasa-reestablishes-historical-art-program-with-space-themed-mural-4/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 21:01 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Defying Gravity</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/5135054500-8ef5339bc9-o/</link>
			<description>A test subject being suited up for studies on the Reduced Gravity Walking Simulator located in the hangar at Langley Research Center. The initial version of this simulator was located inside the hangar. Later a larger version would be located at the Lunar Landing Facility. </description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_34.jpg" length="206325" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/5135054500-8ef5339bc9-o/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:02 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Media Day with Artemis II Crews</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-962/</link>
			<description>From left, CSA (Canadian Space Agency) astronaut Jenni Gibbons, NASA astronaut Andre Douglas, CSA astronaut Jeremy Hansen, and NASA astronauts Christina Koch, Victor Glover, and Reid Wiseman participate in a media day event on Monday, Dec. 16, 2024, inside the Vehicle Assembly Building at the agency’s Kennedy Space Center in Florida.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_35.jpg" length="14923300" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-962/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 18:22 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Best of 2024: Total Solar Eclipse in Indianapolis</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/2024-total-solar-eclipse-3/</link>
			<description>A total solar eclipse is seen from the Indianapolis Motor Speedway, Monday, April 8, 2024, in Indianapolis, Indiana. A total solar eclipse swept across a narrow portion of the North American continent from Mexico’s Pacific coast to the Atlantic coast of Newfoundland, Canada. A partial solar eclipse was visible across the entire North American continent along with parts of Central America and Europe.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_36.jpg" length="2450759" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/2024-total-solar-eclipse-3/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 19:21 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Red and Green Aurora Move Through Earth’s Atmosphere</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/iss072e031823/</link>
			<description>iss072e031823 (Oct. 7, 2024) -- Peering through the window of the SpaceX Dragon Endeavour spacecraft, NASA astronaut Matthew Dominick captured this image of the SpaceX Dragon Freedom spacecraft as vivid green and pink aurora swirled through Earth's atmosphere while the International Space Station soared 273 miles above the Indian Ocean.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_37.jpg" length="6953595" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/iss072e031823/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 19:15 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Remembering President Carter</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/carter-visit-3-2/</link>
			<description>President Carter, wife Rosalynn and daughter Amy are shown a scale model of the crawler that transported the total Shuttle launch configuration to Pad 39 from the Vehicle Assembly Building by NASA's Kennedy Space Center Director, Lee Scherer.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_38.jpg" length="2862176" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/carter-visit-3-2/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 22:11 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hubble Spies a Cosmic Eye</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/hubble-ngc2566-potw2451a/</link>
			<description>This NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope image features the spiral galaxy NGC 2566, which sits 76 million light-years away in the constellation Puppis. A prominent bar of stars stretches across the center of this galaxy, and spiral arms emerge from each end of the bar. Because NGC 2566 appears tilted from our perspective, its disk takes on an almond shape, giving the galaxy the appearance of a cosmic eye.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_39.jpg" length="1662914" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/hubble-ngc2566-potw2451a/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 16:27 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA Runs X-59 Engine in Maximum Afterburner</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/x-59-deck-2-round-2-engine-runs/</link>
			<description>NASA’s X-59 quiet supersonic research aircraft completed its first maximum afterburner test at Lockheed Martin’s Skunk Works facility in Palmdale, California. This full-power test, during which the engine generates additional thrust, validates the additional power needed for meeting the testing conditions of the aircraft. The X-59 is the centerpiece of NASA’s Quesst mission, which aims to overcome a major barrier to supersonic flight over land by reducing the noise of sonic booms.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_40.jpg" length="33310716" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/x-59-deck-2-round-2-engine-runs/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 16:55 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hang a Shining Star Upon the Highest Bough</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ngc2264-2/</link>
			<description>Here is a new version of the “Christmas tree cluster.” NGC 2264 is a cluster of young stars between one and five million years old. (For comparison, the Sun is a middle-aged star about 5 billion years old – about 1,000 times older.)</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_41.jpg" length="1359058" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ngc2264-2/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 19:16 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Commercial Moon Rovers Under Test</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/jsc2024e076712-alt-8f82f3/</link>
			<description>Through NASA’s Artemis campaign, astronauts will land on the lunar surface and use a new generation of spacesuits and rovers as they live, work, and conduct science in the Moon’s South Pole region, exploring more of the lunar surface than ever before. Recently, the agency completed the first round of testing on three commercially owned and developed LTVs (Lunar Terrain Vehicle) from Intuitive Machines, Lunar Outpost, and Venturi Astrolab at NASA’s Johnson Space Center in Houston.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_42.jpg" length="1123018" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/jsc2024e076712-alt-8f82f3/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 20:04 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA’s Terra Satellite Captures 2015 Eclipse Shadow</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gsfc-20171208-archive-e000755orig/</link>
			<description>During the morning of March 20, 2015, a total solar eclipse was visible from parts of Europe, and a partial solar eclipse from northern Africa and northern Asia. NASA's Terra satellite passed over the Arctic Ocean on March 20 at 10:45 UTC (6:45 a.m. EDT) and captured the eclipse's shadow over the clouds in the Arctic Ocean.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_43.jpg" length="10171573" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gsfc-20171208-archive-e000755orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 19:34 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Gateway: Wired for Deep Space</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/a2d590e8-c7df-4f80-9cd4-11a1d20b8123/</link>
			<description>A maze of cables and sensors snakes through a major piece of Gateway, humanity’s first space station around the Moon, during a key testing phase earlier this year to ensure the lunar-orbiting science lab can withstand the harsh conditions of deep space.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_44.jpg" length="799823" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/a2d590e8-c7df-4f80-9cd4-11a1d20b8123/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:10 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Chandra and Webb Spy a Cosmic Wreath</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ngc-602-webb-image-2/</link>
			<description>NGC 602 is a star cluster that lies on the outskirts of the Small Magellanic Cloud, one of the closest galaxies to the Milky Way. This image combines X-rays from NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory and infrared data from NASA's James Webb Space Telescope (JWST).</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_45.jpg" length="33369480" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ngc-602-webb-image-2/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:16 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Artemis II Core Stage Moves to High Bay 2</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-959/</link>
			<description>Teams with NASA’s Exploration Ground Systems transport lower the agency’s 212-foot-tall SLS (Space Launch System) core stage into High Bay 2 at the Vehicle Assembly Building at NASA’s Kennedy Space Center in Florida on Wednesday, Dec. 11, 2024. The one-of-a kind lifting beam is designed to lift the core stage from the transfer aisle to High Bay 2 where it will remain while teams stack the two solid rocket boosters on top of mobile launcher 1 for the SLS core stage.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_46.jpg" length="23047181" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-959/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 22:19 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Atmospheric Probe Takes Flight</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/atmospheric-probe-shows-promise-in-test-flight-2/</link>
			<description>An atmospheric probe model attached upside down to a quad rotor remotely piloted aircraft ascends with the Moon visible on Oct. 22, 2024. The quad rotor aircraft released the probe above Rogers Dry Lake, a flight area adjacent NASA’s Armstrong Flight Research Center in Edwards, California. The probe was designed and built at the center.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_47.jpg" length="8510843" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/atmospheric-probe-shows-promise-in-test-flight-2/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:38 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hubble Captures an Edge-On Spiral with Curve Appeal</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/spiral-from-the-side/</link>
			<description>This NASA/ESA Hubble Space Telescope image features a spiral galaxy, named UGC 10043. Located roughly 150 million light-years from Earth in the constellation Serpens, UGC 10043 is one of the somewhat rare spiral galaxies that we see edge-on.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_48.jpg" length="1476188" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/spiral-from-the-side/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 19:28 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA Astronauts O’Hara and Moghbeli Explore Earth Data</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/expediton-70-astronauts-visit-earth-information-center/</link>
			<description>NASA astronauts Loral O’Hara, left, and Jasmin Moghbeli, right, are seen during a tour of the Earth Information Center, Wednesday, Dec. 4, 2024, at NASA Headquarters in Washington. O’Hara and Moghbeli spent six months in space as part of Expedition 70 aboard the International Space Station.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_49.jpg" length="43081190" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/expediton-70-astronauts-visit-earth-information-center/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 21:04 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mary W. Jackson Portrait Revealed</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/mary-w-jackson-portrait-unveiling-2/</link>
			<description>A portrait of Mary W. Jackson is seen after it was unveiled, Friday, Dec. 6, 2024, at the NASA Headquarters Mary W. Jackson Building in Washington. Mary W. Jackson was a pioneering aerospace engineer and mathematician at NASA’s Langley Research Center.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_50.jpg" length="9485585" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/mary-w-jackson-portrait-unveiling-2/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 19:54 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Orange Lava, Blue Lagoon</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/icelanderuption-oli2-20241124-lrg/</link>
			<description>Landsat 9 captured this image of lava coming from an eruptive fissure near Stóra Skógfell peak on Iceland's Reykjanes peninsula. Lava from the eruption flowed across major roads and closed in on the Blue Lagoon, a popular tourist destination. This natural color scene is overlaid with an infrared signal to help distinguish the lava’s heat signature.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_51.jpg" length="3034600" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/icelanderuption-oli2-20241124-lrg/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 19:46 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Astronaut Suni Williams and Astrobee</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/iss072e189028/</link>
			<description>NASA astronaut and Expedition 72 Commander Suni Williams checks out the Astrobee robotic free-flyer in the Kibo laboratory module outfitted with tentacle-like arms containing gecko-like adhesive pads to demonstrate satellite capture techniques. Development of this robotic technology may increase the life span of satellites and enable the removal of space debris.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_52.jpg" length="4339736" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/iss072e189028/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:51 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Technicians Install Gateway’s Fuel Tanks</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/jsc2024e044854orig/</link>
			<description>Technicians carefully install a piece of equipment to house Gateway’s xenon fuel tanks, part of its advanced electric propulsion system.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_53.jpg" length="1222656" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/jsc2024e044854orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 20:04 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Management and Program Analyst Tami Wisniewski</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ceb-5798/</link>
			<description>“I love my country. I love serving my country. I think that was ingrained in me in the military, where I grew to realize how lucky we are to live in America and have the freedoms that we have. When I returned from [my first duty station] in Germany, I separated from the Air Force for about nine months, but I missed it so much, I was like, 'Well, I guess I could join the reserves." I did want to get my education. I was ready by then.
 
“So, I enrolled in school and went into the Reserves, and then 9/11 happened. That will change a person. I called my unit that afternoon and said, "Whatever you need, I'm ready." I was activated supporting the mission, but I didn't deploy like my husband. [9/11] is what touched my life more than anything: how quickly things can change in the blink of an eye. That's what strengthened my respect of the Air Force core values: service before self and integrity, and excellence in all we do.
 
“Then, when I got pregnant, I thought I might want to be home, so I continued in civil service and just fell in love with my kids. That's when my relationship with loving the Air Force changed. It evolved. I still value all that time I had and served and the lessons I learned growing up [in the Air Force]. The biggest thing I have and will continue to pass on to my kids is respect for your country, even if you don't follow the route I did. Respect your country and the people who serve it.” – Tami Wisniewski, Management and Program Analyst, NASA's Marshall Space Flight Center </description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_54.jpg" length="1238017" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/ceb-5798/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:16 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>John Herrington Performs a Spacewalk</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/0302398orig/</link>
			<description>In this photograph astronaut and STS-113 mission specialist John B. Herrington, (center frame), participates in the mission's third spacewalk. The forward section of the Space Shuttle Endeavour is in right frame.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_55.jpg" length="4500627" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/0302398orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:53 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Selfie Time with Astronaut Victor Glover</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-919/</link>
			<description>NASA astronaut Victor Glover (right) takes photos during a visit on Friday, Nov. 8, 2024, with employees at NASA’s Kennedy Space Center in Florida. The employees support the agency’s Exploration Ground Systems Program to help NASA send astronauts, including Glover, to the Moon and back through the Artemis II launch.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_56.jpg" length="20095711" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/afs-8-101-919/</guid>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:17 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mini NASA Robot Takes a SWIM</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia26423orig/</link>
			<description>This robot prototype was built at NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Southern California to demonstrate the feasibility of a mission concept called SWIM, short for Sensing With Independent Micro-swimmers. SWIM envisions a swarm of dozens of self-propelled, cellphone-size robots exploring the waters of icy moons like Jupiter's Europa and Saturn's Enceladus.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_57.jpg" length="604695" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia26423orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:54 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Icelandic Cyclones</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gsfc-20171208-archive-e002167orig/</link>
			<description>A cyclone is a low-pressure area of winds that spiral inwards. Although tropical storms most often come to mind, these spiraling storms can also form at mid- and high latitudes. Two such cyclones formed in tandem south of Iceland in November 2006.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_58.jpg" length="6107640" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/gsfc-20171208-archive-e002167orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 21:20 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ring Around Tabby’s Star</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia22081orig/</link>
			<description>This illustration depicts a hypothetical uneven ring of dust orbiting KIC 8462852, also known as Boyajian's Star or Tabby's Star. Astronomers have found the dimming of the star over long periods appears to be weaker at longer infrared wavelengths of light and stronger at shorter ultraviolet wavelengths.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_59.jpg" length="382449" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/pia22081orig/</guid>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 19:20 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>STS-129 Crew Aboard the Space Station</title>
			<link>https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/nasa-s-n-1124-80-1f/</link>
			<description>The STS-129 crew members posed for a portrait following a joint news conference on Nov. 24, 2009, with the Expedition 21 crew members (out of frame) on the International Space Station. Pictured (clockwise) from bottom left are astronauts Charles O. Hobaugh, commander; Mike Foreman, Leland Melvin, Robert L. Satcher Jr. and Randy Bresnik, all mission specialists; along with Barry E. Wilmore, pilot; and Nicole Stott, mission specialist.</description>
			<enclosure url="assets/images/nasa-images/image_60.jpg" length="1596526" type="image/jpeg" />
			<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.nasa.gov/image-detail/nasa-s-n-1124-80-1f/</guid>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 21:56 GMT</pubDate>
			<source url="https://www.nasa.gov/feeds/iotd-feed/">NASA Image of the Day</source>
		</item>
</channel>
</rss>